Guide to the Tony Judt Papers MC 233
New York University Archives
- Series IV: Teaching Files
  - Subseries A: Class Material
    - Photocopies in French - Borde, Raymond. “La Fin Du Stalinisme,” Les Temps Modernes No. 129/131, Janv. 1957., undated (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - Photocopies in French - Cachin, Marcel. “Les Événements Historiques De Prague (Février 1948)” Cahiers Du Communisme, No. 7, 1949, undated (Box 18, Folder 72)
    - Photocopies in French - Cayrol, Jean. “A la mémoire de Paul Eluard,” Esprit No. 1, Janv. 1953., undated (Box 18, Folder 73)
    - Photocopies in French - Co., J. “Staline, Le Fantome De Sartre,” Esprit 3, Mars 1957., undated (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - Photocopies in French - Cogniot, Georges. “Les Communistes Et Le Sionisme,” La Nouvelle Critique: Revue Du Marxisme Militant No. 44, Mars 1953., undated (Box 18, Folder 75)
    - Photocopies in French - Dalmas, Luis. “Réflexions Sur Le Communisme Yougoslave (I),” Les Temps Modernes No. 53, Mars 1950., undated (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - Photocopies in French - Dalmas, Luis. “Réflexions Sur Le Communisme Yougoslave (II),” Les Temps Modernes No. 54, Avril 1950., undated (Box 18, Folder 77)
    - Photocopies in French - Dalmas, Luis. “Réflexions Sur Le Communisme Yougoslave (fin),” Les Temps Modernes No. 55, Mai 1950., undated (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Photocopies in French - “Document: La Révolution Hongroise et la Troisième Voie,” Esprit 11, Nov. 1957., undated (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - Photocopies in French - Domenach, Jean-Marie. “La tâche de protestation,” Esprit 1, Janv. 1953., undated (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - Photocopies in French - Domenach, Jean-Marie. “Les Intellectuèls et le Communisme,” Esprit 7, Juil. 1955., undated (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - Photocopies in French - Duclos, Jacques. “Les Événements de Tchécoslovaquie et les Problèmes de la Déemocratie,” Cahiers Du Communisme, No. 4, 1948., undated (Box 18, Folder 82)
    - Photocopies in French - Duclos, Jacques. “Provocations et Crimes De La Clique Tito,” Cahiers Du Communisme, No. 10, 1949., undated (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - Photocopies in French - “…Et Mois Aussi, Je Suis Libre D’Écrire Ce Que Je Veux,” Europe, Mars 1950., undated (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - Photocopies in French - Fejtö, François. “L’Affaire Rajk Quarante Ans Plus Tard,” Vingtieme Siecle Revue D’Histoire, Janv.-Mars 1990., undated (Box 18, Folder 85)
    - Photocopies in French - Fejtö, François. “Premières Leçons D’Une Révolution,” Esprit 12, Dec. 1956., undated (Box 18, Folder 86)
    - Photocopies in French - Figueres, Léo. “L’Édification D’Une Société Nouvelle Dans La République Populaire Fédérative De Yougoslavie,” Cahiers Du Communisme, No. 8-9, 1950., undated (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - Photocopies in French - *Figueres, Léo. “Sur Les Événements du Hongrie,” Cahiers Du Communisme, No. 11, 1956., undated (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - Photocopies in French - “Les Flammes de Budapest,” and Pierre Emmanuel, “Les Oreilles du Roi Midas,” Esprit 12, Dec. 1956., undated (Box 18, Folder 89)
    - Photocopies in French - Jeanson, Francis. “Albert Camus Ou L’Ame Révoltée,” Les Temps Modernes, No. 79, Mai 1952., undated (Box 18, Folder 90)
    - Photocopies in French - Karol, K.S., “L’Avenir Reste Ouvert en Pologne,” in Les Temps Modernes, No. 147-148, Mai-Juin 1958., undated (Box 18, Folder 91)
    - Photocopies in French - Kanapa, Jean. “Opération ‘Kanapa,’” in Les Temps Modernes, No. 100, Mais 1954., undated (Box 18, Folder 92)
    - Photocopies in French - Kolakowski, Leszek. “Responsibilité et Histoire,” in Les Temps Modernes. No. 147-148, Mai-Juin 1958., undated (Box 18, Folder 93)
    - Photocopies in French - Kolakowski, Leszek. “Responsibilité et Histoire (fin),” in Les Temps Modernes. No. 149, Juil 1958., undated (Box 18, Folder 94)
    - Photocopies in French - Labour in Exile, issues 1958-1962, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Photocopies in French - Labour in Exile, issues 1962-1963, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Photocopies in French - Lefort, Claude. “Kravchenko Et Le Probléme De L’U.R.S.S.,” Les Temps Modernes, No. 29, Fev. 1948., undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Photocopies in French - Lefort, Claude. “Le Marxisme et Sartre,” and Sartre response to Lefort in Les Temps Modernes, No. 89, Avr. 1953., undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Photocopies in French - Leibowitz, René. “Le Musicien Engagé (A propos du manifeste des musiciens progressistes de Prague.)” Les Temps Modernes No. 40, Fevr. 1949., undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Photocopies in French - “Un Maitre en Hypocrisie,” Esprit 6, Juin 1957., undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Photocopies in French - Martinet, J.-D. Letter to Les Temps Modernes, response, Les Temps Modernes, No. 57, Juil. 1950., undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Photocopies in French - Merleau-Ponty, M. and Jean-Paul Sartre. “Les Jours De Notre Vie.” Les Temps Modernes, No. 51, Jan. 1950., undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Photocopies in French - Pannonicus, “Après L’Exécution D’Imre Nagy,” Les Temps Modernes. No. 149, Juil. 1958., undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Photocopies in French - Péju, Marcel. “Hier Et Aujourd’hui Le Sens Du Procès Slansky,” in Les Temps Modernes, No. 90. Mai 1953., undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Photocopies in French - Péju, Marcel. “Hier Et Aujourd’hui Le Sens Du Procès Slansky (II),” in Les Temps Modernes, No. 91. Juin 1953., undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Photocopies in French - Péju, Marcel. “Hier Et Aujourd’hui Le Sens Du Procès Slansky (fin),” in Les Temps Modernes, No. 92. Juil. 1953., undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Photocopies in French - Péju, Marcel. “Retour de Pologne,” Les Temps Modernes, No. 137-138, Juil.- Août, 1957., undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Photocopies in French - Pouillon, Jean. “Staline: Catoblépas ou Phénix?” in Les Temps Modernes, No. 103, Juin 1954., undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Photocopies in French - “Rajk Rehabilite,” Esprit 5. Mai 1956., undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Photocopies in French - Sartre, Jean-Paul. “Le Réformisme et Les Fétiches,” Les Temps Modernes, No. 122, Fevr. 1956., undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Photocopies in French - Sartre, Jean-Paul. “Qu’est-ce Que La Littérature?” Les Temps Modernes, No. 17, Fevr. 1947., undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Photocopies in French - Villefosse, Louis de. “Notre Chère Pologne,” Europe, Fevr. 1951., undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Photocopies in French - Wurmser, André. “Pages Polonaises,” Europe, Fevr. 1951., undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Social History (5 lectures), undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Social History (5 lectures), undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Social History (5 lectures), undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - "Julia Minc" in Torańska, Teresa. Them: Stalin's Polish Puppets, undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Western Civ. and 20th c. Europe, undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - French Revolution, circa 1976 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - French Revolution, circa 1976 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - French Revolution, circa 1976 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - French Revolution, circa 1976 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - French Revolution, circa 1976 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - French Revolution, circa 1976 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - French Revolution, circa 1976 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - 12B Europe Since 1870, circa 1979 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - 12B Europe Since 1870, circa 1979 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Socialism, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Socialism - 20th c. left lectures, circa 1983, undated (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Socialism, circa 1983 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Socialism, circa 1983 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Socialism, circa 1983 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Socialism, circa 1983 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Socialism, circa 1983 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Bibliographies, circa 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Bibliographies, circa 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Bibliographies, circa 1978-1988 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Bibliographies, circa 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Bibliographies, circa 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Bibliographies, circa 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Bibliographies, circa 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - 19th c. France, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - 19th c. France, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - 19th c. France, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - 19th c. France, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Socialism and Communism NYU Fall 1988 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Spring 1988 Reading Lists (20th c. France, Western Civ.) (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - 4C Western Civilisation 1815 to present, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - 4C Western Civilisation 1815 to present, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - 4C Western Civilisation 1815 to present, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - 4C Western Civilisation 1815 to present, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - 4C Western Civilisation 1815 to present, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Political Theory and French Thought pre-1890, circa 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Political Theory and French Thought pre-1890, circa 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Political Theory and French Thought pre-1890, circa 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - Political Theory and French Thought pre-1890, circa 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - Political Theory and French Thought pre-1890, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - Bibl. for Paris teaching, Spring '89, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Bibliographies - France, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 65)
    - Bibliographies - France, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 66)
    - Bibliographies - France, circa 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 67)
    - Bibliographies - France, circa 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 68)
    - Bibliographies - France, circa 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 69)
    - Bibliographies - France, circa 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 70)
    - Bibliographies - France, circa 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 71)
    - Bibliographies - France, circa 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 72)
    - Bibliographies - France, circa 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 73)
    - Bibliographies - France, circa 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 74)
    - Bibliographies - France, circa 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 75)
    - Bibliographies - France, circa 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 76)
    - Bibliographies - France, circa 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 77)
    - 20th c. France, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 78)
    - 20th c. France, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 79)
    - History 141C France, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 80)
    - History 141C France, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 81)
    - Between Enlightenment and Suspicion, Fall 1992 (Box 19, Folder 82)
    - French History PhD seminar, circa 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 83)
    - Re-Thinking European History NEH Sem. - reading list, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - G46.2720 Topics in Twentieth Century Political Thought: Blum, Camus, Aron - book lists, circa 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - G46.2720 Topics in Twentieth Century Political Thought: Blum, Camus, Aron - readings, circa 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - G46.2720 Topics in Twentieth Century Political Thought: Blum, Camus, Aron - readings, circa 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - TJ Current Teaching - syllabi, reading lists, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Freshman Honors Seminar - Ironies of (Mis)memory, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Europe Since 1945 - notes. syllabi, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Europe Since 1945 - notes. syllabi, 1999-2005 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Europe Since 1945 - notes. syllabi, 1999-2005 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - French History, 1894-1954-Spring 2000 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - NYU in London-Europe Since 1945: History and Memory, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - NYU in London-Europe Since 1945: History and Memory, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - NYU in London-Identity in Europe, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Europe Since 1945 - G57.2260, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Europe Since 1945 - G57.2260, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - 20th c. Literature of the Field - Spring 2004 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Approaches to Historical Research and Writing-Fall 2005 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Penguin history book catalog, circa 2005 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Penguin history book catalog, circa 2006 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Honors Seminar Spring '06, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Honors Seminar Fall 2007 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Cinema and Society Spring 2008 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Spring 2009: People, Politics and Performance (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Subseries B: Student Files
    General Note
    Discarded - un-annotated copy of Dombrowski Risser, Nicole, France Under Fire: German Invasion, Civilian Flight and Family Survival during World War II, 1940-44
    - Aleem, Saadia, 1996-2001 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Barbarczy, Eszter, 1996-1998 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Barbarczy, Eszter, 1996-1999 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Behm, Anja, 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Brkljocic, Maya, 1997-1999 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Campbell, Elizabeth, 1998-2002 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Campbell, Elizabeth, 1998-2002 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Chamier, Astrid von, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Cooperman, Jessica, 2001-2007 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - CVs and Abstracts, undated (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - CVs and Abstracts, undated (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - CVs and Abstracts, undated (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - CVs and Abstracts, undated (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Daniel, Ana, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Dizikes, Peter, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Dombrowski, Nicole, circa 2004 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Dombrowski, Nicole, circa 2004 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Erikson, Michelle, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Gusia, Linda, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Hallstead, Sheila, 1998-2008 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Hallstead, Sheila, 1998-2008 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Jackson, Harriet, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Jackson, Harriet, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Jackson, Simon, 2005-2009 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Jackson, Simon, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Jackson, Simon, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Jackson, Simon, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Jackson, Simon, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Jackson, Simon, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Jackson, Simon, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Jelliffe, Elizabeth, 1994-1996 (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - Kasevich, Heidi, 1990-1992, undated (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Kelley, Caitlin, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Kelley, Caitlin, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - Kelley, Caitlin, 1993-2006 (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - Kelley, Caitlin, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - Kelley, Caitlin, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - Kelley, Caitlin, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - Kelley, Caitlin, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 62)
    - Kelley, Caitlin, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - Kelley, Caitlin, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 64)
    - Lagos, Katerina, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 65)
    - Lagos, Katerina, circa 2000 (Box 20, Folder 66)
    - Lagos, Katerina, circa 2000 (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - Lagos, Katerina, 1996-1999 (Box 20, Folder 68)
    - Lagos, Katerina, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 69)
    - Lewis, Mary Dewhurst, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Lewis, Mary Dewhurst, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Magloire, Gerarde, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Marker, Emily, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Mendoza, Olivia, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Medve, Marianna, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Merritt, John, 1990-1994 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Merritt, John, 1990-1994 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Merritt, John, 1990-1994 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Michael, Christoph M., 2006 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Misc., 1997-2002 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Misc., 1997-2002 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Misc., 1997-2006 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Misc., 2004-2008 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Molot, Alex, 1999-2001 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Neiman, Agam, 2006-2009 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Oberle, Clara, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Oberle, Clara, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Oberle, Clara, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Oberle, Clara, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Oberle, Clara, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Oberle, Clara, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Oberle, Clara, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Oberle, Clara, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Oberle, Clara, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Oberle, Clara, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Oberle, Clara, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Oberle, Clara, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Opello, Katherine, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Ort, Thomas, 2003, undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Patt, Avi, circa 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Pinto, Michelle, 2005-2006 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Ragan, John David, 1992, undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Riley, Claire, 1991-1998 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Rodrigues, Patricia, 2003-2008 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Rosenbaum, Peter, 1997-2001 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Rudolph, Nicole, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Seikaly, Sherene, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Selwyn, Casey, 2007-2010 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Siskovic, Julie, 1996-1998 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Standley, Michelle, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Stickney, Laura, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Stickney, Laura, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Weiss-Wendt, Anton, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Zabielski, Linda, 1994-1998 (Box 21, Folder 45)
- Series V: Lectures/Conferences/Addresses
  The material in this series is arranged chronologically.
  This series contains material related to Judt's speaking engagements outside of his teaching duties, including notes, outlines and drafts as well as research material. In most cases, the folder contents were clear from their titles. Elsewhere, folder titles were created according to the title of the lecture of where the speech was given.
  - NYIH "We're All Anti-Semites Now," draft, undated (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - "Too Much Memory? World War Two and the Holocaust in Europe Today," draft, undated (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - "What is Left of the Left?", undated (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - "What is Left of the Left?", undated (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - "From Amnesia to Revenge: The Ironies of 'National Revival' in Contemporary Europe," University of Vermont, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - "The Grand Illusion," notes, circa 1995 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - "The Grand Illusion," notes, circa 1995 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Michigan State University lecture: "Minerva's Political Owl: Raymond Aron and the burdens of intellectual responsibility," outline, notes, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Michigan State University lecture: "Minerva's Political Owl: Raymond Aron and the burdens of intellectual responsibility," notes, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Notre Dame, Ball State, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - "Sic Transit Gloria Belli?", circa 1998 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Indiana Spring '99, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Indiana Spring '99, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Council on Foreign Relations conference material, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - "Building States, Building Nations," Oxford, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - "As You Like It? Truth and Illusion in U.S. Foreign Policy,", circa 2003 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - YIVO: Old Demons, New Debates - Anti-Semitism in the West, conference materials, notes, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Nov.-Dec. '03, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Nov.-Dec. '03, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - Williams College 3-11-04: "Goodbye To All That? Anti-Semitism in Europe Past and Present," draft, notes, research, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - World Economic Forum Annual Meeting 2004, Davos, conference materials (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - World Economic Forum Annual Meeting 2004, Davos, conference materials (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - World Economic Forum Annual Meeting 2004, Davos, conference materials, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - 1950s Lecture, notes, circa 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - 1950s Lecture, notes, circa 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - 1950s Lecture, notes, circa 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Vassar College Sitomer Lecture 2-22-05, research, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - "Bonjour Tristesse: The End of the American Dream," 10-5-05, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Princeton: "Very Well, Alone!" 11-22-05, notes, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Einstein Forum, 2005-2006 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Einstein Forum, 2005-2006 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Columbia - "Plaidoyer pour L'Europe Décadente," notes, research, circa 2006 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Columbia - "Plaidoyer pour L'Europe Décadente," notes, research, circa 2006 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Columbia - 3-23-06, notes, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - LRB Israel Lobby Sept. 28, correspondence, notes, research, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - LRB Israel Lobby Sept. 28, correspondence, notes, research, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Book Talks - lectures on Postwar, notes, drafts, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - TJ on Mid-East (school teachers), notes, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - TJ on Mid-East (school teachers), research, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - BC Feb. '07 "Trahison du Clercs," notes, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - University Professorship Lecture 3-2007, draft, notes (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - University Professorship Lecture 3-2007, research, notes (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - University Professorship Lecture 3-2007, research, notes (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Remarque Peace Prize, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - NYR-Oxford conference: "The New Face of American Capitalism," conference material, research, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - NYR-Oxford conference: "The New Face of American Capitalism," research, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - NYR-Oxford conference: "The New Face of American Capitalism," research, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - NYR-Oxford conference: "The New Face of American Capitalism," "Cuckoo Clock" notes, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - NYR-Oxford conference: "The New Face of American Capitalism," "Cuckoo Clock" sources, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - NYR-Oxford conference: Cuckoo Clock for NYR, transcript, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - "The Case for the Cuckoo Clock" notes, circa 2007 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Kreisky, Forum (Israel) June '07 - brochure, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Kreisky, Lecture - June '07 - draft, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Finkelstein & Walt-Mearsheimer 10-12-07 (U. of Chicago academic freedom forum), correspondence, research, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Finkelstein & Walt-Mearsheimer 10-12-07 (U. of Chicago academic freedom forum), research, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Princeton and Aron, Oct. '07, "In Defense of Decadent Europe" draft, notes, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Kanderstag II Notes (Remarque seminar in Switzerland), correspondence, notes, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Kanderstag II Notes (Remarque seminar in Switzerland), CVs, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Kanderstag II Notes (Remarque seminar in Switzerland), CVs, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - ENS Talk Nov. '07, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Rothschild January 24 "The Problem of Evil," notes, research, circa 2008 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Riverdale - "On Jewish Responsibility" Feb. '08, draft, notes, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Remarque Lecture: "What is Living and What is Dead in Social Democracy?" research, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Remarque Lecture: "What is Living and What is Dead in Social Democracy?" research, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Remarque Lecture: "What is Living and What is Dead in Social Democracy?" research, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Remarque Lecture: "What is Living and What is Dead in Social Democracy?" research, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Remarque Lecture: "What is Living and What is Dead in Social Democracy?" research, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Remarque Lecture: "What is Living and What is Dead in Social Democracy?" research, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Remarque Lecture: "What is Living and What is Dead in Social Democracy?" research, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Remarque Lecture: "What is Living and What is Dead in Social Democracy?" research, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Remarque Lecture: "What is Living and What is Dead in Social Democracy?" notes, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Remarque Lecture: "What is Living and What is Dead in Social Democracy?" notes, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 46)